Welcome dear customer,
welcome to Lau Look, where we are celebrating Black Friday.
Come in and discover the best prices.
The payment method in our store are bells,
we do not accept fossil, fish or bugs as a payment method.
Welcome, welcome customer, welcome.
Over here, come over here.
What do you think of our first product?
These are seven competition medals from different sports,
with the name of a person that's not you engraved on them.
Its hard metal guarantees a durability of more than 10 years,
while its striking colored ribbons add a touch that will bring life to your living room.
This is the perfect product to hang in your home
or to wear around your neck as a decoration.
It's quite a bargain.
I would like to show you the eighth wonder of the world.
No, sorry, the ninth. The eighth is a microwave brownie.
This key opens absolutely everything.
Our experts have proven it and there is nothing that these keys cannot open.
These keys due to their incredible utility have a unique price of 1200 bells.
Changes or refunds are not accepted.
Our next product is the mikado.
In case you don't know mikado,
this is a board game made up of 26 sticks
decorated with different colors and patterns,
and the aim of the game is to get the maximum number of sticks
without the rest moving a millimeter.
What we are going to sell you will be two sticks.
These two sticks, being only two,
can be used to eat, like chopsticks.
And you can also play a quick game of mikado.
We are going to turn this product into a collection,
so that you can buy two sticks every month.
With a subscription of 70 bells per month.
Quite a bargain.
This following may seem like a simple product and that's because it is.
This is the cover of this wonderful movie called Under Suspicion,
in which Thomas Jane and Monica Bellucci star.
It's a great movie.
And the best thing is that it does not have a CD, we only sell the cover.
The outside is what matters, right?
This next product goes with Carolina's communion mini CD.
If you don't have a place to keep Carolina's communion,
then you can use Under Suspicion -
and they will make the perfect match.
Combining both products would result in a bargain of just 2,000 bells.
2000 bells.
I am going to add it directly to your basket because it is clear that you want to buy this product at half price.
I'll put it in the basket.
I don't know if you know Strawberry Shortcake.
No, not this strawberry shortcake this Strawberry Shortcake.
Two years ago my cousins ​​visited Strawberry Shortcake and made a butcher shop out of her.
This is Strawberry Shortcake now.
Well what we sell is strawberry shortcake hair.
It is a high quality product.
Smells like strawberry.
I have nothing else to say other than that this
is the best purchase you can make this Black Friday.
This one here is a product coveted by many.
What is called an exceptional piece.
This is something that is no longer produced, it is no longer manufactured.
It is the case of an ipod touch.
I feel like it is no longer for sale because the ipod touch box just broke.
My sincerest apologies, dear customer.
Ehm, if I can't help you right now, I'm with a client.
Drop off my order at the back door--
Yes--
Yes, I want 2,500 ipod touch boxes.
Yes.
Let no one find out that they are still making them please.
Ok, thank you very much, see you later.
I thought I had gone to checkout to pay dear customer.
You haven't heard my phone conversation, have you?
All right, come with me, come with me.
Let's go to the checkout to pay.
What?
You don't have bells?
I'm sorry?
You haven't brought bells to pay?
You only have fish?
Security, security! Take him away from here.
I hope you enjoyed the video dear customer.
Leave in a comment which product you would like to buy.
Although we are very busy for being our week of Black Friday of 2020,
we assure you a delivery of the product in a period of between 2 to 3 days,
directly to your door.
We hope you have been satisfied with our services,
so please like and subscribe.
Bye.